Anthony Westmoreland

Team Lead, Principal Solutions Engineer

westmoreland.anthony@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Diligent technologist with a creative edge. Over 10 years of SaaS solution selling expertise across Ad/Martech and IoT in SMB and Enterprise. I believe that data should drive decision making and success is achieved through specificity and accountability.

TECHNICAL AND LANGUAGE SKILLS

Adobe Marketing Cloud, SalesForce, xCode, Postman, Eclipse, Charles Proxy, JIRA, Basecamp, Data & Analytics, AdTech Platforms, Digital Marketing Technology, AWS, Snowflake, Google Suite, Mobile Development, C(++), Cocoa, HTML/CSS, Python, JavaScript, XSL/XML, Swift, Objective-C, JSON

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Team Lead, Principal Solutions Engineer, mParticle, Mar 2019 - Present

- Top performing Solutions Engineer in 2018 & 2019, closing highest total revenue and volume of new customers. Subset of customers won in 2019 include AMC Networks, Mars, Reverb, and Restaurant Brands International (Burger King, Popeye's, and Tim Hortons).
- Reduced onboarding time for new Solutions Engineers over 40% by creating enablement framework that was leveraged for all Technical Services team members and the basis of enabling new Account Executives
- Expanded mParticle's global presence by closing first LATAM customer (Televisa), working as both the Account Executive and Solutions Engineer.
- Pioneered a new Product Demo format that closed a \$1M+ account within 30 days.
- Consistent feedback from prospects to senior management regarding the "quality of service, level of integrity, and transparency" in which I ran sales cycles, and being the "strongest technical sales contact" through both technical and non-technical evaluations.

Principal Solutions Engineer, mParticle, Mar 2017 – Mar 2019

Sole Sales Engineer of East Sales Team, working with 8 Account Executives, managing 40% of potential new revenue (deals in Stage 3 or higher), and averaging a close rate of 70% once deals reached Stage 3. | Built senior and executive level relationships with key business stakeholders, by providing strategic advice and technical solutions to achieve a digital transformation. | Developed custom applications across web, app, IoT, etc integrating the mParticle solution into a prospects' future architecture.

Global, Dr Tech Services and Support, Celtra, Inc, Mar 2015 – Mar 2017 Sales Engineer / Director of Technical Services, Celtra, September 2012 – March 2015

- Grew Tech Services team from 3 members to 12 members over 3 years, while reducing ramp time to under 90 days.
- Analyzed Global Desk support ticket data, identifying trends that evened distribution of workload across team, automated 20% of responses, and maintained an average support ticket lifetime of less than 4 hours.
- Implemented new experience for prospects to test Celtra, which eliminated repetitive work and increased team efficiency 10%.

PREVIOUS ROLES

- Sales Engineer, Medialets, September 2010 July 2011
- Engagement/Project Manager, BigMachines Inc, Chicago, IL, September 2009 2010

EDUCATION

NC State University, B.S. Computer & Electrical Engineering, May 2008 Varsity Athlete 3Y / ROTC 4 Semesters